{
    "id": "55e6b1ab226a4eac9e14af6d0a9948b1",
    "title": "Simple Present Or Present Continuous Tense",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Every morning, my dad ………….. for a walk in the park.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "go",
                "goes",
                "is going"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f4ea49a563c1441dbd1764996b151a98"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………. some old friends this week.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "visit",
                "am visiting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "087b1035ff8349e887f848a4c9cbad58"
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t make a noise. The baby ......................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "sleeps",
                "sleeping",
                "is sleeping"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "a8c98b092e6d4f0a81ca5a948c5997ac"
        },
        {
            "question": "The kettle …………………. Shall I make tea?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "boils",
                "is boiling"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "914a5a3c4c0145de827f3cdb6c90c055"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………. this wine very much.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "like",
                "am liking"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d890044da2304865b2f250062a0b17fb"
        },
        {
            "question": "Don’t forget to take your umbrella. It ..........................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "rains",
                "is raining"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "8d7589411a9b44f786dc074a351c2e30"
        },
        {
            "question": "She doesn’t like to be disturbed if she .........................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "works",
                "is working"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "efa132767df34172bd4f2ec90462a2bc"
        },
        {
            "question": "My brother ………………. in Paris at the moment.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "works",
                "is working"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "161913de2cb445cc9962c5d7ae53f0c0"
        },
        {
            "question": "He …………………. his grandparents about twice a year.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "visit",
                "visits",
                "is visiting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "56f4f9cfda9e46798adf4db30e2bd38a"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………….. what he says.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "not believe",
                "don't believe",
                "am not believing"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "9e9701cc59fd466a92ce44a8e5d6ab86"
        }
    ]
}